And once you realize that I am Kira, we're getting married!
そして…俺がキラだとわかってもらえたら、結婚だ！
So, as you all can hear... Higuchi is Kira!
と、いうわけで…
火口がキラです！
Guidance
If the killing of criminals cease now, there would be no doubt that Higuchi has Kira's power.
犯罪者殺しが止まれば、
火口がキラの能力を持っていると考えて間違いない
If the killing of criminals cease now, there would be no doubt that Higuchi has Kira's power.
However... although I've always thought that Amane would go a long way to help Yagami Light out
しかし…
However... although I've always thought that Amane would go a long way to help Yagami Light out,
弥が夜神月の為に、
ある程度はやってくれるとは考えていたが…
I never realized she'd go this far.
ここまでしてしまうとは…
Now that she's gone this far and stopped the killings... it'll become even more difficult to witness the actual method they use to kill.
犯罪者殺しまで止まってしまったら、
肝心の殺し方を見るのが難しくなる
Now that she's gone this far and stopped the killings... it'll become even more difficult to witness the actual method they use to kill.
I need to think of a plan...
何か策を考えなければ…
Misa, how did you manage to get Higuchi to confess?
海砂、これをどうやって火口に言わせたんだ？
Huh? Oh, that guy's totally crazy about Misa.
え？あいつ、海砂にメロメロだもん
I told him that I'd marry Kira.
「キラなら結婚する」って言ったんだよ
Plus, he's already convinced that Misa is the second Kira.
それにあいつ、海砂を第二のキラだと思い込んでるし
Unless I say this now, I might end up contradicting myself later on...
こう言っておかないと、後で矛盾出てきちゃいそうだし…
Idiot!
馬鹿
Didn't I tell you to deny that, no matter what?!
そこだけは必ず否定しろと、言ったはずだ！
B-But now we know Higuchi is Kira. All we've got to do is catch him.
で…でも、もうこれで火口がキラなんだから
捕まえればいいだけじゃない
This is what you might call "nice work", right, Matsuda-san?
こういうのを手柄って言うんでしょうか、松田さん
Yet, as things stand, we're still no closer to discovering how he kills.
しかしこの状況では、まだ殺し方がわからない
Yeah, that's right.
そうなんですよね…
Before I capture him, I want to know how he kills...
火口を捕まえるより先に、どうして殺してるかが欲しい…
And if the killing of criminals cease, you won't be able to see how he kills, isn't that right?
そして、犯罪者の死が止まったら、その殺し方が見られない
そうだな？
Yes. In any case, even though we're going to capture Higuchi,
はい
どうせ火口を捕まえるにしても、
犯罪者が死ななくなったと断定してからです
that won't be until after we've determined that the judging of criminals has ceased.
Please allow me to think about this...
少し考えさせてください
Weddy?
ウエディ
Yes?
はい
How's the situation?
どうですか？状況は
It's looking good.
良好よ
The movements of those seven can be tracked about 70% of the time, while inside the company building.
会社の中の七人の行動なら、
七割くらいまでならカメラで追えそう
What about outside of the company?
会社の外なら？
With just Watari and myself, it's impossible.
それは私とワタリだけでは無理よ
What if we were to solely focus on Higuchi?
火口に絞ったらどうなりますか？
Higuchi?
火口？
So far, I've only entered five of their houses, but Midou, Namikawa and Higuchi's houses have security systems that aren't normal.
まだ五人しか家の中には入ってないけど
三堂、奈南川、火口の家は、普通のセキュリティじゃない
So far, I've only entered five of their houses, but Midou, Namikawa and Higuchi's houses have security systems that aren't normal.
In particular, Higuchi has recently build a basement that blocks electromagnetic waves.
特に火口は、電波を遮断した地下室を最近造っていて
It even took me a full two days to infiltrate that place.
私でも侵入に二日を要した
Just as we thought, Higuchi is definitely suspicious.
やはり火口、怪しいですね
Understood. In that case, install bugging equipment, transmitters and cameras in Higuchi's car rather than his house.
わかりました
では家ではなく、
火口の車に盗聴器、発信器、カメラをお願いします
Eh?! After going through all that?!
え？ここまでやって…
Do you have any idea of how hard it is to break into someone's house?!
人の家に入るのどれだけ大変かわかってる？
Besides, do you even know how many cars Higuchi owns?!
それに、火口何台車持ってると思う？
Six.
六台です
Okay, fine. You want me to do all of them, right?
…わかった
火口の車全部につければいいのね
Yes please.
お願いします
Woah... if they had done that a little earlier, it would have been dangerous...
うわっ…もっと早くこの盗聴やられてたらヤバかった
Yagami-kun... I'm sorry to bring this up again, but let me ask you this directly:
夜神君
話が戻って悪いんですが…
Yagami-kun... I'm sorry to bring this up again, but let me ask you this directly:
もう単刀直入に聞きます
What is it?
なんだ？
Do you remember killing them?
殺したことを…覚えていますか？
You still insist on saying that?! I am not Kira!
まだそんなこと言ってるのか…
僕はキラじゃない
How many times do I have to te--
何度言えばわか…
Please, just answer the question.
質問に答えてください
Do you remember?
覚えていますか？
…覚えてない
I don't remember.
What about Misa-san?
海砂さんはどうですか？
I don't remember anything because I'm not Kira!
覚えてませんし、キラとかじゃありませんから
Yagami-kun, I need you to consider these assumptions and analyze it earnestly.
夜神君
私が今から言う事を、真剣に推理、分析してみてください
Your answer may be the first step in capturing Kira.
その答え次第で、キラを捕まえることに踏み切れます
Yagami Light was Kira.
夜神月はキラだった
Kira's powers were then transferred to someone else.
ちから
そしてキラの能力は他に渡った…
Now Yagami Light has absolutely no memory of being Kira.
今、夜神月はキラだったということを忘れている…
That will be the premise behind this analysis.
これを前提にした分析です
Will you be able to think on that basis?
そういう考え方は、できますか？
Yeah, I'll give it a try.
ああ…やってみよう
Yagami Light was Kira.
夜神月はキラだった…
Kira's powers were then transferred to someone else.
ちから
そしてキラの能力は人に渡った…
Was this transfer done by Yagami Light's own will?
これは夜神月の意思で渡ったのか？
Or was there someone else behind Yagami Light, who bestowed Kira's power, and transferred that power from Yagami Light to another?
ちから
それとも、夜神月の裏にキラの能力を与えていた者がいて
夜神月から…他の人間に移したのか？
With those presumptions... it'd have been by Yagami Light's own will.
その前提なら、夜神月の意思だ
That's right...
…そうですよね
If there was a human behind the scenes who could bestow and transfer that power... and they didn't want their methods discovered...
もし、与えたり移せたりできる人間が裏にいて、
殺し方を知られたくないのなら
It's a little suspicious that they hadn't transferred until right at the very last moment...
あのギリギリまで他に移さなかったのはおかしい
And if we accept the existence of something that could look down on us from heaven, there would be no way to catch it.
天から見通せる様な者の存在を認めたら、
そんな者は捕まえようがないし
And if we accept the existence of something that could look down on us from heaven, there would be no way to catch it.
I would either have died a long time ago, or I'd be spending eternity being toyed with in the palm of their hand.
私は、とっくに殺されているか
永遠に手の平の上で遊ばれ続けるか…です
I would either have died a long time ago, or I'd be spending eternity being toyed with in the palm of their hand.
There's no way that something like that exists.
そんな者の存在など、あり得ない…
Even if Yagami Light was Kira...
夜神月がキラであったとしても…
Only the current Kira can use that power.
ちから　　　　　ちから
キラの能力は、能力を持った者の意思でしか動かない
Yagami-kun... thanks to that, I'm feeling 99% better.
夜神君
お蔭で９９％はすっきりしました
We'll create a situation where Higuchi will not pass the power on to anyone else... and let him show us how he kills people.
ちから
火口が自分から人に能力を渡さない状況を作って、
殺し方を見せてもらいます
We'll create a situation where Higuchi will not pass the power on to anyone else... and let him show us how he kills people.
What are you planning?
どうするんだ？
I'm going to use Sakura TV to trap Higuchi.
さくらテレビを使って火口を引っ掛けます
You mean Dokkiri TV?!
Dokkiri TV is the Japanese version of Candid Camera.
ドッキリテレビだ
What's that?
何それ？
We'll utilize the "Kira Special" that Demegawa continues to broadcast.
出目川が今でも毎週やっている「キラ特番」
We'll arrange a three-hour show, and at the beginning of it, we'll announce that "We'll reveal Kira's identity by the end of this show!"
３時間枠を取らせ、冒頭で
「番組の最後までには、キラが誰なのか発表する」と言う
Is he going to believe that? After all, it's on Sakura TV, right?
そんなの信じるかな…
それも、さくらテレビでしょ？
Besides, Higuchi might not even watch that program.
大体火口がその番組観ないかもしれないし…
All we've got to do is contact Namikawa and ask him to call Higuchi and say: "There's trouble brewing, turn on the TV".
奈南川に連絡し、火口に：
「まずい、すぐにテレビを見ろ」と電話させるだけでいい
If Higuchi sees someone who may know his secret, he'll believe it.
そして、そのテレビに出ている者が秘密を知る者だとわかれば
火口は信じる
I see! You're planning to use Aiber.
なるほど、アイバーを使うんだ
You're going to reveal that in reality he was a spy!
実はスパイだって、ばらしちゃうんですね
No, you're totally wrong. I'm not planning to use Aiber.
全然違います
アイバーは使えません
No, you're totally wrong. I'm not planning to use Aiber.
The person Higuchi sees on TV needs to be someone that he thinks he'll be able to kill, otherwise there's no point.
火口がそのテレビ番組の出演者を見て、
殺せると思える者でないと、ダメです
To be blunt, it has to be someone whose name he thinks he could quickly and easily find if he tries.
つまり名前を調べようとすれば…すぐ調べられそうな者
Is there even such a person around?
そんな人、いますかね
It's got to be Matsuda-san.
松田さんしかいない
Matsu!
マッツー
Matsuda, huh?
松田か…
Higuchi believes that you were trying to eavesdrop on their meeting,
火口は、松田さんが会議を盗み聞きしていたと思うし
so if the supposedly dead manager begins to threaten to expose everything, he'll believe it.
死んだはずのマネージャが、暴露しようとしてるなら信じる
He's right.
そうです
We'll get Sakura TV to prepare a screen and a microphone the way they usually do with witnesses.
さくらテレビには、証言者用の擦りガラスとマイクを用意させる
From the silhouette and from what's being said, Higuchi should be able to work out that it's "Manager Matsui".
火口はその発表とシルエットからでも
松井マネージャと気づくでしょう
Furthermore, we'll have the station "slip up" and momentarily reveal the face of the person behind the screen.
さらに局のミスで一瞬、
擦りガラスの向こうの人物の顔が映ってしまう
Cool! Sounds fun!
うわっ、面白そう
And he'll announce that by the end of the show, he'll reveal the full identity of "H", better known as Kira.
そして番組終了までには、キラである H の本名を発表するという
エイチ
Kira's identity will be announced at the end of this show!
キラの正体は、番組の最後に！
Placed in that situation, all Higuchi will be concerned about, is how fast he'll be able to find out the manager's real name.
この状況では、
火口は一秒でも早く、名前を知る事しか考えられない
We can predict Higuchi's actions.
火口の動きは予想できる
And then, we'll be able to confirm exactly how he's been killing people.
そして殺し方を確認…然る後、確保
If this plan has a flaw, it's that...
今のところこの策に問題があるとすれば…
If Higuchi is similar to the second Kira, and can kill someone solely by knowing their face...
もし火口が第二のキラの様に、顔だけで殺せることがあれば…
松田さんが死にます
Matsuda-san will die.
But given that Matsuda-san is still alive, and that Higuchi wants Misa, I'd say it was unlikely.
それも今、松田さんが生きている事
海砂を欲しがっている事から、多分ないだろう
But given that Matsuda-san is still alive, and that Higuchi wants Misa, I'd say it was unlikely.
We'll only be using this plan if criminals stop dying though.
まぁ、犯罪者の死が止まったらの策ですし
We'll need to give it two to three days to be sure.
止まるかどうかは二、三日見なければなりません
You can make your own decision on whether or not to go ahead with it during this time, Matsuda-san.
やるかどうか、その間に松田さん自身が決めてください
I don't need two or three days.
二、三日なんていりませんよ…
Please, allow me to do it.
やらせてください
So, what's the deal with this secret meeting then?
コソコソと何の相談だ？
Namikawa, who do you think is Kira?
奈南川…
誰かキラだと思う？
What's the point in asking that?
それを聞いてどうするんだ？
It could even be you, Shimura, or you, Midou.
大体、紙村かもしれないし
三堂かもしれないじゃないか
No, it's not Shimura.
いや、紙村はない
He came crying to me about how he could no longer go along with Kira's evil ways.
私に「もうキラの悪事にはついていけない」と…泣きついた
Shimura, if Midou was Kira, you'd be dead.
紙村、三堂がキラだったら殺されてたな
No, you and Midou would have had successful lives regardless of all this.
いや、三堂や奈南川は放っておいたって出世するし
八人で死の会議なんて馬鹿なことをするはずがない
Neither of you would do something so stupid as to call an eight-person meeting to discuss murder.
Even I am able to figure out that much.
俺だってそのくらいはわかる
The only reason everyone's going along with this is because they're all scared of being killed by Kira.
皆キラに殺されるのを恐れて…合わせてるだけだ
But if we continue this way, we'll be caught sooner or later.
しかしこのまま続けていたって、いつかは世間にバレる
No, in fact, unless that happens, it'll never end.
いや、そうならなければ…終わらない
では紙村、逆に聞くが、誰がキラだと思ってる
Well then, Shimura, let me ask you the same question. Who do you think is Kira?
Takahashi or Higuchi.
鷹橋か火口…
Takahashi merely acts as a foil for Kira.
鷹橋はキラの引き立て役だ
It's necessary that Kira has someone who's not as smart as him.
キラより考えの浅い者もいないとまずい
ふっ…
Seems like everyone has already figured this out...
皆大体わかってるんじゃないか
It's likely that it's Higuchi.
火口だろうな
Yeah. Higuchi is the one who desires money and promotion the most.
ああ…
出世や金に一番貪欲なのは火口だ
He's always talking about how he doesn't care for promotion, but conversely this just shows how hung up he really is about it.
いつも「出世なんて」と口癖のように言っているのが
逆にこだわっている証拠だ
He berates people, but doesn't know how to manage them,
そのくせ人を馬鹿にし、うまく使う事もできず
and as a result he has been demoted from Director of Development to merely the Head of a Development lab.
開発部長から開発室長に格下げだからな
Am I the only one who you've asked to come here?
ここに来るよう声を掛けたのは、私だけか？
We asked Ooi, but he said that we're free to have our pathetic little meeting without him.
尾々井にも声を掛けたんだが…
「そんなくだらない密談、勝手にやってくれ」だそうだ
We asked Ooi, but he said that we're free to have our pathetic little meeting without him.
ふふ…大ざっぱな尾々井らしい
Typical of Ooi, always brash.
Since Kida had to organize Coil's commission, plus the finances for it, he's not Kira either.
樹多も、
コイルへの依頼運営資金の口座提供をさせられたことから
キラではない
Since Kida had to organize Coil's commission, plus the finances for it, he's not Kira either.
Namikawa, after Hatori died, you received a phone call during the next meeting... who was it?
奈南川、葉鳥が死んだ後の会議中、電話がかかってきただろ
あれはなんだ？
Shimura, you're really shrewd, aren't you?
紙村、お前は、本当に目敏いな…
Kira must have chosen you for your prudence.
その注意深さを買って、キラはメンバーに入れたんだろう…
Namikawa.
奈南川だ
This is L. Namikawa-san, are you alone right now?
L です
奈南川さん…今一人ですか？
No...
いや
In that case, please act naturally like before.
ではまた適当に相槌を
There's no need for that.
その必要はない
Currently, I'm with some people who've realized that the call I received from you during that meeting was odd.
会議中にあなたからもらった電話が変だと気づいた者といるんだ
Who's on the phone, Namikawa?
何だその電話…奈南川
It's L.
L だ
L, I've got both Midou and Shimura with me.
L 、ここに三堂と紙村がいるが
It's unlikely that either of them is Kira, and both are annoyed with Kira.
二人ともキラとは思えないし、キラに腹を立ててる口だ
Whatever happens, they're both happy to sit on the sidelines and watch this thing between L and Kira unfold, just like me.
何を言われても、私のように L とキラの決着を見守るだろう
That's fine.
いいでしょう
Tonight, we'll capture Kira, but we'll need your help.
今夜キラを捕まえる
少し協力して欲しい
フッ…
So, this is the end for Higuchi...
火口も再期か…
終り
You knew?
わかっていたのか？
フフッ… L でも引っかかるんですね
I guess even L can be tricked.
今のあなたの反応で、１００％火口になりました
Thanks to your response, I'm now 100% sure that it's Higuchi.
奈南川ってやるね
Namikawa's pretty good! Looking at his face, Misa thought he might be smart...
あの人の顔はそこそこやると思ってたの、海砂
No, that was a mistake on Yagami-kun's part.
いいえ、夜神君の失敗です
Tonight, we'll be using the "Kira Special" shown on Sakura TV at 7pm to force Higuchi's hand.
今夜７時からの、さくらテレビのキラ特集で…火口を動かす
I need you to contact Higuchi a few minutes after the program has started, and tell him to watch the TV.
番組が始まって数分後に、
火口にテレビを見る様に連絡を入れて欲しい
I promise that the remaining six of you won't be adversely affected.
他の六人は絶対に悪いようにはしない…
If Kida, Takahashi or Ooi attempt anything... I need you to stop them.
そこにいない樹多、鷹橋、
尾々井が何かしようとしたら、止めてください
If Kida, Takahashi or Ooi attempt anything... I need you to stop them.
ああ…わかった
Okay...
やはり火口だそうだ
Looks like it really is Higuchi.
He'll probably be caught tonight.
今夜多分…捕まる
It's been three days since I stopped judging criminals.
犯罪者の裁きを止めて三日、そろそろいいだろう
That should be enough...
If I marry the second Kira, Amane, I'll have the Shinigami's Eyes, and I'll be able to control Yotsuba completely!
これで第二のキラ、弥と結婚すれば
死神の目も手に入る
そしてこの俺が…ヨツバの全てを支配するのだ
Higuchi, this looks bad. Turn on Sakura TV.
火口、まずい、テレビを見ろ
さくらテレビだ
では、その中の一人が…キラなんですね
So, you're saying one of them is Kira, right?
はい、証拠はたくさんあるんです
Yes, and I've got plenty of proof.
What the hell is this?
なんだこれは、どうせデマだろ
It's bound to be fake. After all, this is Sakura TV we're talking about.
さくらテレビだぞ
At the beginning of the program he stated; "I overheard a meeting between eight people".
それが一番最初に、
「八人で会議をしていた所に遭遇した」と言ったんだ
会議の事を知っている者…
Someone who knows about the meetings?!
Who?! Has someone betrayed us?!
誰だ…誰が裏切ったのか…
And then one of them was killed, so now there's only seven.
そして、そのうちの一人が殺されて、七人に…
The victim was Mr. "H".
犠牲になったのは、 H さんです
エイチ
"H"? Hatori...
H …　葉鳥…
エイチ
"H"? Hatori...
Knowing this much, he's either one of the other six... or Coil.
ここまで知っているとなると、他の六人か…
いや、コイル
Knowing this much, he's either one of the other six... or Coil.
Mr. "H" was killed because he wanted out of those meetings.
H さんは、その会議から抜けたいと言ってキラに殺されました
エイチ
No, none of them would gain a thing from doing this.
いや…あいつ等がこんな事して、得になる事はない…
Yet, there shouldn't be anyone else who'd know about these meetings...
しかし、他にあの会議を知っている者なんて…
ん？いや、こいつ…
T-This guy...
I-It's him?!
あ…あいつだ！
He used to be Misa's manager, I think his name was Matsui. Why the hell is he still alive?!
海砂のマネージャだった、確か松井…
何故生きている…!?
He gambled on faking a fall from a high rise apartment, because he thought he was going to be killed,
殺されると思って、一か八かマンションから落ちる振りをして
下の階のベランダに逃れたと…さっき喋っていた
and escaped by landing on the veranda on the floor below, or so he said earlier.
No, afterwards I wrote the name on his business card into the Death Note, just in case...
いや…私は念のため、家に帰ってから
奴の名刺を見て、名前をノートに書いた…
Why is he still alive?!
何故生きてる…
元タレントで、芸名のままマネージャになったとか…
Perhaps he was in the business previously, and kept his stage name when he became a manager... or something...
I don't get it!
わからん
In addition, he says that he's been investigating Yotsuba and knows who Kira is.
しかもこいつ、その後ずっと一人でヨツバを調べまわり
誰かキラなのかわかったと…
I'm in the process of contacting everyone now.
今、皆に連絡している
Okay, I'll hang up for now.
わかった、一度切るぞ
About the accident just now, are you alright? Would you like to stop?
先程のアクシデント…大丈夫ですか？
もう止めますか？
About the accident just now, are you alright? Would you like to stop?
いえ…元々危険は承知です
No, I knew that I'd be letting myself in for trouble from the beginning.
Even if I die, I'll try my best until the end - in the name of justice!
正義の為に、殺されようと
…最後まで頑張ります！
Nice, nice... as long as you ensure you don't make the announcement until the end of the program.
いいぞ、いいぞ
あくまでもキラの発表は番組の最後まで言うんじゃないぞ
I've got no choice but to kill him!
殺すしかない…
The second Kira, Misa, will know his name as well as his face...
第二のキラである海砂なら、
顔はもちろんのこと、名前も知っている…
来た
It's here!
What the hell is going on?!
なんだ、おい！
It's taken me a while to come to this decision and make this announcement, but ever since I found out the truth,
正直、発表を決断するまでは、かなり悩みましたが
知った以上、発表するのが人間だと決心しました
I've felt that as a human being, I must persevere.
まずいな…
This is bad... I could be exposed at any moment.
That announcement isn't far off now. Stay tuned!
その発表は、まもなくです
いつ暴露されるか…
チャンネルはそのまま
Cosme Misa. Brilliant gloss.
Cosme Misa
小悪魔の艶
天使の輝き
An angel's sparkle. Misa's Cashmere Rouge.
Misa ☆の勝ち組ルージュ　発進
三堂、俺だ
Midou? It's me. Sakura TV is causing trouble.
さくらテレビがまずい
Your father is in the House of Councilors, right?
参院にいるお前の親父から
Get him to put pressure on the Ministry of Public Affairs and put a stop to this program.
また総務省に手を回して、番組を止めさせよう
I'm watching it too, and it would be impossible.
私も観てるが、それは無理だ
No one is going to believe this, and doing that will just make it look suspicious.
誰もこの番組を信用してないし、逆に疑われる
Anyway, there's no need to worry.
それに、もう何も心配ないじゃないか
His face was on TV, so we were able to identify him as Matsui Tarou.
さっき顔がテレビに映り、あの松井太郎と確認できた
Namikawa contacted everyone and told them to watch the TV.
奈南川からテレビを見ろとの連絡は皆に回っている
Since one of us seven is Kira, Matsui Tarou will soon be dead.
七人のうちの誰かがキラだから、松井太郎はまもなく死ぬ
そうか…
I see! As Kira, I'm the only one who's realized that "Matsui Tarou" is a fake name!
松井太郎が本名でないとわかっているのは、キラである俺だけ…
それを言えば、キラだという事をバラす事になる…
If I tell them that, they'll know I'm Kira.
みなさん、もうすぐキラの正体が、明らかになります
Everyone! Soon Kira's identity will become clear! Stay tuned!
そうだな、じゃあな
Guess you're right. See ya.
どうか、お付き合いください
Damn it!
くそ…!!
竜崎、火口から、
ヨシダプロ前で張っている、模木さんに電話が入りました
Ryuuzaki, Higuchi is calling Mogi-san, who's outside Yoshida Productions.
はい、次来ましたね
Yes, here it comes. Just as we planned.
予定通りです
Moji! Where's Misa?!
模地、海砂はどこだ？
Ah, Higuchi-sama, thank you so much for doing business with us!
あっ、お世話になっております、火口様
Misa is currently having one of her rare days off, so she has gone out.
Misa ☆はただいま久々のオフで、出掛けております
She should be back tomorrow morning...
明日の朝には帰ると…はい
I'm asking you where she went.
どこに出掛けだと聞いてるんだ
I'm sorry, but she said it was private and left without telling anyone.
それが…プライベートなので、誰にも知られたくないと…
I'm terribly sorry. I'll be able to contact her tomorrow.
申し訳ございません
明日には連絡がつくかと
Damn it! I know his face. If only I knew his name, I could...
くそ…顔はわかっているんだ
名前さえわかれば、いつでも…
Her former manager, was he in show business?
前のマネージャーのあれ、元タレントか？
Huh?
はい？
"Matsui Tarou", remember?!
松井太郎っていただろ？
ああ…入れ代わりで入ったので、私は何とも…
I replaced him, so I can't really tell you more.
For such inquiries, you should try calling the office.
そういう事でしたら、事務所の方に…
Oh! But they're all presently in Okinawa. Maybe you could try the President?
あ…でも、今皆で沖縄に来ているんで
社長に電話して頂けますか？
This is going so precisely as planned, it's almost scary.
まったく筋書き通りで、怖いくらいだな
怖がらず喜びましょう、夜神君
Let's not be scared. Just sit back and enjoy this, Yagami-kun.
I'll relay the call between Higuchi and the President of Yoshida Productions.
火口から、ヨシダプロ社長に中継します
This is Higuchi of the Yotsuba Group.
ヨツバの火口だが…
That guy who used to work for you, Matsui Tarou, was that his real name?
前にいた松井太郎って、本名じゃないのか？
He's getting more and more direct. Higuchi is such a fool.
段々聞き方がストレートになってきてるね
Ah yes, he was using a stage name when he was a manager, Higuchi-san.
ああ、彼はマネージャーとしての名前を使っていたんですよ、火口さん
火口の馬鹿
It shows that he's getting desperate.
余裕がなくなってきている証拠です
そうか…
What's his real name?
本名は？
I think it's Yamada... no, wait! It's Yamashita.
確か…山田…いや、山下
As for his first name... I can't remember.
下の名前は…
覚えていませんね
Don't fuck with me! You should at least know the names of the people you employ!
ふざけるな！
雇った人間の名前ぐらい、覚えておけ！
Hey, there's no need for that kind of talk.
何ですか？その言い方…
If you go to the office it should be in the records.
事務所に戻れば、ちゃんと履歴書もとってあるし…
Well, go and tell me.
じゃあ、戻って教えろ
Gimme a break, we're on the first staff trip we've had in two years!
いやもう、勘弁してくださいよ
こっちは二年ぶりの社員旅行なんです
But if you insist, I'll give you the combination code to access the office.
ここまで言うなら、事務所のロックの暗証番号を教えますから
入って見て頂いて構いませんよ
I don't mind if you go and check it out yourself.
The records are kept in the bottom drawer of the far left hand side desk as you enter.
履歴書は、入って左の奥の机の一番下の引き出しです
ちゃんと「あいうえお」順になっています
They're ordered alphabetically. I think it should be Yamashita.
多分、山下です
番組の最後に言うのであれば…
If they're planning on announcing it at the end of the program, I've still got two hours.
まだ二時間ある…
I wonder if he'll make a move...
動くかな？
火口確認
Higuchi's status confirmed.
所持品はバックのみ、追います
I'm in pursuit.
Until now, everything has gone exactly as we predicted.
ここまでは、思惑通りだな
Yes...
はい
I'll kill him... for sure!
必ず、殺してやる…
ここまで来て、潰されてたまるか…
After coming this far, I'm not going to be defeated... I'm going to get it all!
俺は…全てを手に入れるんだ！
To be continued
これで俺は最強だ
くそっ、こんな物使いたくはないが
火口は拳銃を所持、局長が撃たれました！
なんかまずいじゃない？
おい火口、抜け駆けはなしだ
これで視聴率１００％に間違いなしだ、なははははは…
違う！知らない！
観念するのね
よく考えるんだ
ここまでだ
間に合った！